Ricketts mss. III, 1856-1979 LMC 1831
Lilly Library
- Financial
  - Invoices
    - The Franklin Company - Chicago, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 142)
    - Franklin MacVeagh & Co., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 143)
    - Frazier, Walter, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Free Methodist Church of North America, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - Fuest, Mme. Clara, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - Gage Brothers & Co., 1911 (Box 15, Folder 147)
    - Gardner, Corbus P., 1912 (Box 15, Folder 148)
    - Gardner, Harry A., 1926 (Box 15, Folder 149)
    - Gardner, Henry A., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - Garrett Biblical Institute / Theological Seminary, 1908-1965 (Box 15, Folder 151)
      See also Northwestern University, 1896, Apr. 25; Chicago Training School, 1938-1942
    - General Box Company, 1924 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - General Electric Company, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - General Outdoor Advertising, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 154)
    - George Spies, Inc. / Industries, 1939-1961 (Box 15, Folder 155)
    - The German-American Hospital - Chicago, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 156)
    - The German Hospital of Chicago, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 157)
    - Der Germania Maennerchor, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 158)
    - Girl Scouts of Chicago, 1955-1956 (Box 15, Folder 159)
    - Gisholt Machine Company, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 160)
    - Glencoe (village), Illinois, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 161)
    - Glencoe, Illinois - Board of Education, 1905-1913 (Box 15, Folder 162)
    - Glencoe, Illinois - Lodge 983, A.F. and A.M., 1925 (Box 15, Folder 163)
    - Glencoe Union Church, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 164)
    - Glenwood Manual Training School, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 165)
    - Goethe Monument Association of Chicago, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 166)
    - Goodwin, John S., 1915-1917 (Box 15, Folder 167)
    - Gorton School - Lake Forest, Illinois, 1947-1955 (Box 15, Folder 168)
    - Gottschalk Lyric School, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 169)
    - Grable's Gift and Art Galleries, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 170)
    - Grace Church, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 171)
    - Grace Church - Hinsdale, Illinois, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 172)
    - Grand Beach, Michigan, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    - Grand Lodge of Ancient Free Masons of Chicago, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 174)
    - Grand Lodge of Ancient Free Masons of South Carolina, 1935-1968 (Box 15, Folder 175)
    - Grannis, C. O., 1921 (Box 15, Folder 176)
    - Grant Hospital of Chicago, 1919-1925 (Box 15, Folder 177)
    - Great Lakes Dredge and Dock Co., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 178)
    - Great Northern Railway Co., 1914 (Box 15, Folder 179)
    - Green, Robert F., 1916 (Box 15, Folder 180)
      Regarding the death of his daughter Margaret Green, a friend of Julia Ricketts
    - Greensburg School Board - Pennsylvania, 1909-1911 (Box 15, Folder 181)
    - Gregg-Moore Co., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 182)
    - The Gunn School of Music and Dramatic Art, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 183)
    - Gunsaulus, Frank W., 1916 (Box 15, Folder 184)
    - H. M. Harper and Co., 1964 (Box 15, Folder 185)
    - Hadley Correspondence School for the Blind, 1939-1941 (Box 15, Folder 186)
    - Hahn, Manuel, 1941 (Box 15, Folder 187)
    - Hahnemann Hospital - Chicago, 1904-1914 (Box 15, Folder 188)
    - Hamill, Alfred Ernest, 1914-1924 (Box 15, Folder 189)
    - Hall, Richard C., 1914 (Box 15, Folder 190)
    - Harris Trust and Savings Bank, 1918-1962 (Box 15, Folder 191)
    - The Harvard Club of Chicago, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Harvard Community High School - Illinois, 1939 (Box 15, Folder 193)
    - The Harvard School for Boys - Chicago, 1909-1942 (Box 15, Folder 194)
    - Hart, Schaffner and Marx - Chicago, 1918-1919 (Box 15, Folder 195)
    - Haskall and Barker Car Co., 1911 (Box 15, Folder 196)
    - Hastings College - Nebraska, 1922-1926 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - Hebrew Theological College - Chicago, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Heckman, Wallace, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Heinemann, H. E. O., 1918 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - The Henry O. Shepard Co., 1906 (Box 15, Folder 201)
      See also in "Memorials, Resolutions, and Testimonials" subseries for sir Thomas Lipton, 1906
    - Hesperia Lodge, No. 441 A.F. and A.M., 1916 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Hibbard, R. E., 1937 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - Hibbard, Spencer, Bartlett and Co., 1915 (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Highland Park Parent-Teacher Association - Illinois, 1940 (Box 15, Folder 205)
    - Highland Park Presbyterian Church, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Highland Park School District 107 - Illinois, 1908-1936 (Box 15, Folder 207)
    - Highland Park School District 113 - Illinois, 1940-1961 (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - Hill, R. D., 1913 (Box 15, Folder 209)
    - Hill School Club of Chicago, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 210)
    - Hinckley, Sumner P., 1946 (Box 15, Folder 211)
    - Hines, Edward, 1925-1926 (Box 15, Folder 212)
    - Hinsdale Board of Education - Illinois, 1909-1912 (Box 15, Folder 213)
    - Hinsdale Sanitarium and Hospital, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 214)
    - Hiram Walker, Inc., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 215)
    - Holabird and Roche, Architects, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 216)
    - The Holland Society, 1896 (Box 15, Folder 217)
    - Hopkins, Sutter, Owen and Mulroy, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 218)
    - Hornberger, Robert E., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 219)
    - Hornell, New York - Board of Education, 1907-1911 (Box 15, Folder 220)
    - Horsley, Frank, 1915 (Box 15, Folder 221)
    - Horton, Arthur B., 1961-1966 (Box 15, Folder 222)
    - The Hotel Association of Chicago, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 223)
    - Huiskamp, Henry W., 1911-1913 (Box 15, Folder 224)
      This is the "Henry" spoken of in the early letters of Hettie
    - Hunter, Robert H., 1923 (Box 15, Folder 225)
    - Huron College - South Dakota, 1908-1942 (Box 15, Folder 226)
    - Hyde Park Baptist Sunday School - Chicago, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 227)
    - The Illini Club of Chicago, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 228)
    - Illinois Association of Merchandise Warehousemen, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 229)
    - Illinois Audubon Society, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 230)
    - Illinois Bankers Association, 1911-1942 (Box 15, Folder 231)
    - Illinois Bell Telephone Co., 1924-1940 (Box 15, Folder 232)
    - Illinois Board of Higher Education, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 233)
    - Illinois Central Railroad, 1919-1967 (Box 15, Folder 234)
    - Illinois Coal Operators Association, 1911-1916 (Box 15, Folder 235)
    - Illinois College, 1912-1940 (Box 15, Folder 236)
    - the Illinois Commercial Hotel Association, 1911 (Box 15, Folder 237)
    - Illinois Farm Supply Co., 1957 (Box 15, Folder 238)
    - Illinois Institute of Technology, 1942 (Box 15, Folder 239)
    - Illinois Library Association, 1949-1964 (Box 15, Folder 240)
    - Illinois Life Insurance Company, 1924-1925 (Box 15, Folder 241)
    - Illinois Mining Institute, 1958-1966 (Box 15, Folder 242)
    - Illinois Northern Utilities Co., 1942 (Box 15, Folder 243)
    - Illinois Osteopathic Association, 1949-1951 (Box 15, Folder 244)
    - Illinois Society of Certified Public Accountants, 1914-1942 (Box 15, Folder 245)
    - Illinois (State), 1918 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Illinois State Brewers' Association, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Illinois State Chamber of Commerce, 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Illinois - State Council of Defense, 1918-1924 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Illinois State Dental Society, 1911-1919 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Illinois State Geological Survey, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Illinois Steele Co., 1914-1925 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Illinois Sunday School Association, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Illinois Training School for Nurses, 1906-1923 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Imperial Brass / Imperial Eastman Company, 1951-1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Independent Pneumatic Tool Co., 1918-1923 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Independent Voters of Illinois, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Indiana Natural Gas and Oil Co., 1910 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Industrial Editors Association, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Inland Lake Yachting Association, 1942-1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Inland Steel Co., 1917-1961 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Inland Steel Container Co., 1965 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - The Institute of Medicine of Chicago, 1958-1976 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - International Business Machines, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - International Celucotton Products Co., 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The International Dairy Show, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - International Harvester Co., 1924 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - International House - Chicago, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - International Stewards Association, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - International Sunday School Association, 1911-1917 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - International Technological Institute, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Interstate Bakeries Corporation, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Investment Bankers Association of America, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Isham, H. P., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - The James C. King Home for Old Men, 1913-1914 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - James White Paper Co., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Jennings Seminary, Aurora, Illinois, 1912-1926 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Jewish Charities of Chicago, 1924-1930 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Jewish Home Finding Society, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Jewish Training School, 1914-1919 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - The John Crerar Library, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - The John Howard Society, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 37)
      See letter: June 12, 1967
    - Johnson, Vilas, 1940-1942 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Jones, Alfred, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Jones, Thomas Davies, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Judah, Mrs. Noble B., 1920 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Junior Association of Commerce, 1940-1942 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Juvenile Protective Association, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Kabo Corset Co., 1915-1924 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Kay, Warren, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Kenwood Club - Chicago, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Kimball, Ronald M., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Kimberly-Clark Corp., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Kimmell, William B., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - King-Bruwaert House, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Kings County Lighting Co., 1911-1913 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Kiwanis Club International, 1920-1921 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Knight, Augustus, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Knight, Eustace J., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Kopyright Office Supplies, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Kranz, John, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - La Crosse Lutheran Hospital, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Ladies Catholic Benevolent Association, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Lafayette Chapter, No. 2 - Royal Arch Masons, 1915-1927 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Laird and Lee, 1906-1909 (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Lake Forest Academy Alumni Association, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Lake Forest, Illinois - Board of Education, 1919-1942 (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Lake Forest University / College, 1929-1963 (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Lake Geneva Water Power and Lake Level Protection Co., 1908 (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Lake Geneva Yacht Club, 1944-1964 (Box 16, Folder 65)
      See also: Inland Lakes Yachting Association
    - Lake Shore Country Club, 1916-1936 (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Lakeside Hospital, 1904-1912 (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Lake View High School Alumni Association - Chicago, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - La Rabida Jackson Park Sanitarium, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Larimer, Howard S., 1937 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - Les Cheneaux Club, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - Libby, McNeill and Libby, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Liberty Trust and Savings Bank, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Lincoln Printing Co., 1926 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Lindblom, Robert, 1897 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Littelfuse, Inc., 1966 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Live Stock Exchange National Bank, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Locomotive Fire Box Co., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - Loeb, Jacob M., 1915 (Box 16, Folder 79)
    - Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 80)
    - The Lovers of Italy, 1909 (Box 16, Folder 81)
    - Loyola University - Chicago, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 82)
    - Luther College - Decorah, Iowa, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 83)
    - Lyon and Healy, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 84)
    - Lyon Metal Products, Inc., 1942-1957 (Box 16, Folder 85)
    - Lyons Township High School - La Grange, Illinois, 1908-1939 (Box 16, Folder 86)
    - McCormick, Mrs. Cyrus Hall, 1893 (Box 16, Folder 87)
    - McCormick Theological Seminary, 1911-1924 (Box 16, Folder 88)
    - McCoy and Wildman, Drs., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 89)
    - McLaughlin, James A., 1926 (Box 16, Folder 90)
    - Maggs Brothers, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Marquette Cement Manufacturing Co., 1925-1926 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Marshall Field and Co., 1928-1942 (Box 16, Folder 93)
    - Mary Thompson Hospital, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 94)
    - Mascot Copper co., 1917 (Box 16, Folder 95)
    - Mather, William J., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 96)
    - Matthiessen and Heheler Zinc Co., 1924 (Box 16, Folder 97)
    - Maximum Savings Society of Illinois, 1919 (Box 16, Folder 98)
    - Medical Library Association, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 99)
    - The Members Group C.R.P., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 100)
    - Mercantile National Bank - Hammond, Indiana, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 101)
    - Merchant Tailors and Designers Association of Chicago, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 102)
    - The Merchants Loan and Trust Co. of Chicago, 1911-1918 (Box 16, Folder 103)
    - Methodist Church - Board of Hospitals and Homes, 1948-1966 (Box 16, Folder 104)
    - Methodist Hospital - Indianapolis, Indiana, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 105)
    - Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council - Chicago, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 106)
    - Michael Reese Hospital, 1896-1912 (Box 16, Folder 107)
    - Michigan State Dental Association, 1958-1964 (Box 16, Folder 108)
    - Mid-America Hearing Foundation, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 109)
    - Mid-City Trust and Savings Bank - Chicago, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 110)
    - Mid-Day Club, Chicago, 1938-1966 (Box 16, Folder 111)
    - Military Order of the Loyal Legion of the U.S. of America, 1917 (Box 16, Folder 112)
    - Milwaukee-Downer Seminary, 1926-1937 (Box 16, Folder 113)
    - The Milwaukee Road, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 114)
    - Mitchell, Ernest, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 115)
    - Morgan Park Military Academy, 1922-1938 (Box 16, Folder 116)
    - Morris and Company, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 117)
    - Morton Salt Co., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 118)
    - Mosser, Edward J., 1923-1925 (Box 16, Folder 119)
    - Mount Olive Cemetery Assoc., 1923-1926 (Box 16, Folder 120)
    - Municipal Art League of Chicago, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 121)
    - Munising Paper Co., 1939 (Box 16, Folder 122)
    - Munroe and Southworth, Chicago, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 123)
    - Museum of Science and Industry - Chicago, 1936-1959 (Box 16, Folder 124)
    - Muskegon, Michigan - Board of Education, 1907-1926 (Box 16, Folder 125)
    - Naperville Seminary, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 126)
    - Nashota House Wisconsin, 1957-1965 (Box 16, Folder 127)
    - National Aluminate Corporation, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - National Association of Real Estate Boards, 1924-1941 (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - National Association of Talking Machine Jobbers, 1917-1918 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - National Bank of the Republic, 1912-1925 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - National Bond and Investment Co., 1941 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - National City Bank of Chicago, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - National College of Education, 1935-1942 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - National Conference of Business Paper Editors, 1926 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - National Conference of Industrial Editors Association, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 136)
    - National Container Association, 1939
    - The National Dairy Cattle Congress, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 138)
    - National Dental Association, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 139)
    - National Electric Light Association, 1917-1926 (Box 16, Folder 140)
    - National Glass Distributors Association, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 141)
    - National Interfraternity Conference, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 142)
    - National Medical University - Chicago, 1905-1908 (Box 16, Folder 143)
    - National Metal Trades Association, 1913-1918 (Box 16, Folder 144)
    - National Methodist Town and Country Conference, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 145)
    - National Mileage Co. - Evanston, Illinois, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 146)
    - National Prohibition Party, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 147)
    - National Railway Appliances Association, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 148)
    - National School/Institute for Commercial and Trade Organization Executives, 1924-1951 (Box 16, Folder 149)
    - National Restaurant Association, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 150)
    - National Standard Co., 1942-1959 (Box 16, Folder 151)
    - Newberry Library, 1914-1942 (Box 16, Folder 152)
    - Newsboys and Bootblacks Association, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 153)
    - New Trier Township High School - Winnetka, Illinois, 1942-1979 (Box 16, Folder 154)
    - New York Central Lines - General Agents Association, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Nine Hundred Michigan Avenue North Corporation, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - Nineteen Forty One Caucus Committee, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 157)
    - Nineteen Thirty Eight Caucus Committee, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 158)
    - Norris, Frederick A., 1918 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - North Central Association, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - North Suburban Academy of Dental Research, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - Northbrook Skating Club, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Northern Paper Mills, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 163)
    - The Northern Trust Co., 1914-1957 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - Northwest Academy of Dental Medicine, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - Northwestern Elevated Railroad Co., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - Northwestern Life Insurance Co. - Association of Agents, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - Northwestern Trust Co., 1917 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - Northwestern University, 1896-1957 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - Norwegian-American Hospital, 1936 (Box 16, Folder 170)
    - Norwegian National League, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 171)
    - Oak Park Business Men's Association, 1913-1915 (Box 16, Folder 172)
    - Oberfelder, Herbert M., 1926-1942 (Box 16, Folder 173)
    - Oberfelder, Joseph H., 1929 (Box 16, Folder 174)
    - O'Brien, James R., 1927 (Box 16, Folder 175)
    - Old Republic Life Insurance Co., 1951-1967 (Box 16, Folder 176)
    - One North La Salle Corporation, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 177)
    - The Onwentsia Club, 1914-1916 (Box 16, Folder 178)
    - Oppenheim, Sidney, 1938 (Box 16, Folder 179)
    - The Orchestral Association, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    - Osato, W., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 181)
    - Ottawa Silica Co. - Illinois, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 182)
    - Pabst Sales Co., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 183)
    - Pacific American Fisheries, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 184)
    - Page, John Mitchell, 1916 (Box 16, Folder 185)
    - Palmolive Co., 1921 (Box 16, Folder 186)
    - Park Employees' Annuity and Benefit Fund - Chicago, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    - Park Ridge Presbyterian Church, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 188)
    - Passavant Memorial Hospital School of Nursing, 1932-1963 (Box 16, Folder 189)
    - Pattison, Mr., 1916 (Box 16, Folder 190)
    - Peabody, Mass. - Board of Education, 1914-1918 (Box 16, Folder 191)
    - Pekin Community High School, Illinois, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 192)
    - Penfield, Louis C., 1923 (Box 16, Folder 193)
    - The Peoples Church, Chicago, 1932? (Box 16, Folder 194)
    - Peoples Gas Light and Coke Co., 1909-1938 (Box 16, Folder 195)
    - Peoples Stock Yards State Bank, 1913-1918 (Box 16, Folder 196)
    - Perkins Products Co., 1953 (Box 16, Folder 197)
    - Pettibone, Mrs. P. J., 1896 (Box 16, Folder 198)
    - Pheoll Manufacturing Co., 1924 (Box 16, Folder 199)
    - Phi Kappa Phi Honor Society, 1924 (Box 16, Folder 200)
    - Phoenix Insurance Co. of Hartford, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 201)
    - Ping, Mrs. J. J., 1967 (Box 16, Folder 202)
    - Pioneer Paper Stock Co., 1942 (Box 16, Folder 203)
    - Plan for Hospital Care, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 204)
    - Plee-Zing, Inc., 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Plimpton, George A., 1911 (Box 16, Folder 206)
    - Polish National Alliance, 1922 (Box 16, Folder 207)
    - Porter, H. H., 1935 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - Post Advertising Co., 1957 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Post Graduate Medical School, 1896-1910 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Practical Refrigerating Engineers Association, 1955-1976 (Box 16, Folder 211)
    - The Prairie Farmer, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - The Presbyterian Home, 1941-1946 (Box 16, Folder 213)
    - Presbyterian Hospital, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Presbyterian Theological Seminary, 1937-1942 (Box 16, Folder 215)
    - Presler, Frances, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Princeton Club of Chicago, 1912 (Box 16, Folder 217)
    - Prudence Crandall Club, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 218)
      This is a copy of an invoice made in 1929 by CLR [lb] Prudence Crandall, 1803-1889, philanthropist, was persecuted because she opened a school for women of color in Rhode Island
    - Psi Upsilon Fraternity, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 219)
    - Public Service Co. of Northern Illinois, 1917-1940 (Box 16, Folder 220)
    - The Pullman Co., 1916-1918 (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Purdue University, 1939-1942 (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - Queen Insurance Co., 1904-1905 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Quill and Scroll Society, 1936-1938 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - R. R. Donnelly and Sons Co., 1915-1922 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - The Racquet Club, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 226)
    - Railway and Locomotive Historical Society, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 227)
    - Railway Business Association, 1918-1942 (Box 16, Folder 228)
    - Rainbow Lodge, No. 972, A.F. and A.M., 1915 (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Randall, Clarence B., 1937-1938 (Box 16, Folder 230)
    - Randolph Box and Label Co., 1913 (Box 16, Folder 231)
    - Ravina Festival Association, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 232)
    - Rawson, Frederick H., 1906 (Box 16, Folder 233)
    - Rawson, Stephen W., 1893 (Box 16, Folder 234)
    - Raymond, E. H., 1915 (Box 16, Folder 235)
    - Red Book Magazine, 1913-1915 (Box 16, Folder 236)
    - Reed, C. I., 1925 (Box 16, Folder 237)
    - Rehabilitation Institute of Chicago, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 238)
    - Reincke, Meyer and Finn, 1950-1965 (Box 16, Folder 239)
    - Republican Executive Committee, 1894 (Box 16, Folder 240)
    - The Retail Drygoods Association of Chicago, 1907 (Box 16, Folder 241)
    - Rice, F. Willis, 1911 (Box 16, Folder 242)
    - Ricketts, C. L., 1930 (Box 16, Folder 243)
    - River Forest Library Board - Chicago, Illinois, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 244)
    - Riverside, Illinois - Board of Education, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 245)
    - Robert Appleton Co., 1912-1913 (Box 16, Folder 246)
    - Robert Bartlett Realty Co., 1938 (Box 16, Folder 247)
    - Roche, Williams and Cleary, Inc., 1952-1958 (Box 16, Folder 248)
    - Rockford College, Illinois, 1936-1940 (Box 16, Folder 249)
    - Roosevelt University, Chicago, 1968-1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Rotary Club - Chicago, 1941-1958 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Rotary Club - International, 1913-1926 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Rotary Club - Wilmette, Illinois, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Rotary Club - Winnetka, Illinois, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Royal Arch Masons, Pullman Chapter, No. 204, 1918 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Royal Arcanum of Illinois, 1912 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Roycemore School - Evanston, Illinois, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Rush Medical College, Chicago, 1910-1924 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - S. A. Sprague Memorial Institute, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Saint Ambrose Academy/School, 1912-1923 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Saint Bernard's Hotel Dieu/Hospital, 1909-1941 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - St. Cyril's College - Chicago, 1908-1921 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Saint Gregory Choir School - Chicago, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 14)